Zhijiang Capacity Infinite Technology (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Technology Co., Ltd.
Musician Han is absolutely the best in Fangzhou.
Bravo!
That sounds so beautiful.
He truly lives up to his name as Musician Han.
Who are you?
Tell us your name.
From the Western Regions,
Ashina Xiao.
It's the Zither Demon of the Western Regions.
I heard of him when I was trading there.
Those who challenged him in zither playing
all met a bad end.
What do you want?
I came to Fangzhou for a three-day zither duel.
If I successfully hold the ring after three days,
the so-called grand zither music of Huaxia
is nothing but a piece of trash
on the road to the Western Regions.
This is going too far!
I'll smash your arena right now!
Yeah!
My head hurts so much.
Musician Han,
my head hurts so much.
What's wrong with you?
Musician Han!
Is he... is he dead?
Brother Chu,
do you like it?
Three days.
I'll be waiting for you.
What is his name again?
Ashina Xiao.
Hurry and report it to the yamen!
Last night,
our famous Fangzhou zither player, Han Se...
Died competing in a zither battle with the Western Regions zitherist Ashina Xiao.
That Ashina Xiao even said
our Hua Xia zither music isn't worth a single hair of the Western Regions'.
Can we tolerate this?
If he has the guts, compete in swordplay.
I'll chop him into minced meat.
They challenge you to a zither battle,
and you use a sword.
Isn't that embarrassing?
Can a zither battle really kill someone?
I've heard something about it.
This person
is known as the Zither Demon of the Western Regions,
and the human bone zither he uses is even more sinister.
I heard Musician Han died a gruesome death.
It must be the work of evil forces again.
Investigate this case thoroughly.
How can we let a lowly zitherist
be so arrogant within the borders of our Great Tang?
Yes.
Wangzhou is established under Xishi.
I heard about this man.
He challenged others to a zither competition for three days,
and even wanted Prince Ling to announce it to the world.
Where does this kid from the Western Regions get the nerve?
I heard he just
competed with the best musician in Fangzhou and killed him.
Yeah.
His head split open.
I'm confused.
This isn't a zither competition.
It's clearly a murder.
You are Ashina Xiao?
I'm Su Yao from the county office.
Come with me to the office.
What if I don't go?
This zither sound can indeed capture people's souls.
I want to see
if his zither is fiercer or my sword is faster.
I'm Su Yao from the county office.
Come with me to the office.
Those who don't leave after hearing my zither
are not simple people.
If I'm not wrong,
you two must be the famous detective Su
and Mr. Shen from Fangzhou.
I heard your zither sound can kill.
Have you ever heard that a zither sound can kill?
It's clearly because your Tang musicians are not skilled enough,
and died of shame.
Don't falsely accuse me of murder.
You!
Wait.
Aren't there still two days left?
When the time comes,
someone will naturally deal with you.
You'd better not let us catch any flaws.
Let's go.
Stop listening.
Go home.
Master.
Why did you leave?
I am unfilial.
I watched you
being killed by that demon from the Western Regions.
Don't worry, Master.
I will definitely avenge you.
I will make Ashina Xiao
be buried with you.
That sounds nice.
That zither demon is in the market.
Why didn't you challenge him?
Qingluan.
What do you mean?
As the eldest disciple,
I should bury Master first.
Even Master couldn't defeat that zither demon.
You going there is just a suicide.
You!
You've always been disrespectful to your elders.
They say the eldest brother is like a father.
Since Master is not here today,
I will teach you a lesson for him.
What kind of eldest disciple are you? Come on!
Brothers.
Brothers, stop fighting.
Stop it.
Don't pull me.
Brothers, stop fighting.
What's the noise?
Brothers,
stop fighting.
Master's body is not yet cold.
You are fighting here.
What a scandal!
Lord Su,
why are you here?
Master Han was the best musician in Fangzhou.
He competed with Ashina Xiao this time.
His death was suspicious.
So we're here to investigate.
Constable Su,
this is an internal matter of the Music Academy.
We don't need your help.
How can you let our master die in vain?
It's not your place to speak!
The day Master Han died suddenly,
someone
heard Ashina Xiao shout Chu Feng's name.
Who is Chu Feng?
He is our junior brother.
Ten years ago,
he was also the best musician in Fangzhou.
But he was also the most arrogant and insane musician.
So handsome.
Chu Feng,
you took all the scores.
What are we going to play?
You don't deserve to practice.
Get out of here!
Bravo!
He wouldn't board the emperor's boat,
calling himself an immortal of wine.
Bravo!
Amazing!
Junior Brother Chu Feng,
why did you take things so hard?
The world has lost its music.
The way of the qin is dead.
He committed suicide.
Yes.
He was like Dugu Qiubai.
He could never find a rival,
and felt extremely empty.
He became possessed by the qin.
Tell me,
isn't it a pity?
If Chu Feng were here.
How dare you let this scoundrel from the Western Regions be so arrogant!
You have to be obsessed to succeed.
Junior Brother Chu Feng had slender fingers,
sharp ears, and keen eyes.
He was truly a rare and talented lutenist.
What a pity.
He acted domineering and unrestrained,
which eventually backfired
and caused a tragedy.
Who is playing the lute?
Master.
A zombie!
Pull me!
Close it!
Yes.
Push harder!
The lute music. It's the lute music.
Stop!
I told you to stop playing!